Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 1: Building Project Records, 1879-2002 July 2; 91 boxes
  - Dormitory Fire Protection, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Murray Theater - Purchase Orders, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Frick, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Green Hall - Electron Microscope Lab, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Green Hall, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Palmer Lab - Decontamination, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Palmer Hall, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Palmer Hall, 1972-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Princeton Inn, 1969-1979; 1 box
    - Kitchen - Floor Project, 1975; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Furniture and Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Municipality, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - University, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Job Meetings, Etc, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Addition, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - College, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Addition, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Furniture, 1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Addition, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Budget and Fees, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Purchase Orders, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Purchase Orders, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Green Hall, 1969; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - 169-171 Nassau Street - Purchase Orders, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - 169-171 Nassau Street - Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - 169-171 Nassau Street, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Dillon Gym, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Guggenheim Lab, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Jones/Palmer - Purchase Orders, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Palmer Hall, 1972-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Jones/Palmer Library, 1971-1973; 4 folders (Box 34, Folder 23-26)
  - Palmer Hall, 1968-1974; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Jones/Palmer - Purchase Orders, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Architectural Master Plan - Montclair State College Reports, 1968; 1 box
    - I - Basic Data, 1968; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - II - Master Plan Development, 1968; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - III - Master Plan, 1968; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Natural Resource Inventory - West Windsor, New Jersey, 1979 March; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Department of Grounds and Buildings - Building Data Computer Printouts A-H, 1960-1976; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Department of Grounds and Buildings - Building Data Computer Printouts I-Z, 1960-1976; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Graduate College, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Department of Grounds and Buildings - Building Data, 1960-1976; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Revised General Ordinances - Township of South Brunswick, 1975; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Revised Ordinances of Princeton, New Jersey, 1964; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Computer Aided Campus Planning for Colleges and Universities - Interim Report, 1967 August; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Development Plan, 1961 March; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Legal and Institutional Framework for Long Island Sound Management, 1974 November; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Annotated Bibliography on University Planning and Development", 1968 December; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "A Long range Plan for Harvard University and Radcliffe College in Cambridge and Allston - Interim Report", 1974 June; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "The New Campus in Britain: Ideas of Consequence for the United States", 1966; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Nacubo Professional Program - Assorted Brochures and Forms, 1980; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Master Plan - Township of East Brunswick, New Jersey, 1976 May 19; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ten Designs for Community Colleges - Rice University, 1962; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Directory of Subsidized Rental Housing, 1978 January; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Princeton University, "Land Planning and Housing Potentials: A Preliminary Assessment", 1970 October; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey - Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1977; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Cini-Grissom Associates - Catalogue, 1981; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Worksheets, 1975; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Green Hall Annex - Aaron Burr Hall, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Engineering Quad, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Student Space Data, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Data as Noted - Buildings, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Jones/Palmer Library, 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Jones/Palmer Library, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - New South - Completed Jobs, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Graduate College Mail Room, 1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Macmillan Building - Purchase Orders, 1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Macmillan Building, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Witherspoon Hall, 1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Frick, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Green Annex - Purchase Orders, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Madison Hall, 1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Aero Lab, 1969; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - 99 Alexander, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Student Center Alterations, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - 185 Nassau Street - Photo Lab, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Photo Lab - 185 Nassau, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Chemical Sciences Building, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - McCosh 104, 1974; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Jones Hall, 1973; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Caldwell Field House, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Baker Rink, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Palmer Stadium, 1974; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Clio Hall, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - 83 Prospect, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Alexander Hall, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Chancellor Green, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Grounds, Russell, Rapuano, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Life Sciences, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Life Sciences - Budget, Miscellaneous, 1974; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Public Disclosure, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Wilson College, 1975; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Green Hall Annex, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 185 Nassau Street, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - West College, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Quad Addition, 1969-1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Building 25, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Whig Hall, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Terrace Club, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Prospect Avenue Clubs, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Armory, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Jones Hall, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Garden Theater, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Palmer Hall, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Moffett Lab - Applebury, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Moffett Lab - Cold Room, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Moffett - M-35, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Grounds, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Engineering Quad, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - McCosh 50, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Engineering Quad, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Engineering Quad, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Green Hall, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Joseph Henry House, 1974; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Palmer House - Housing Study, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Architecture, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Engineering Quad, 1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Moffett - II, 1976; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Frick, 1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Moffett - III, 1976; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Moffett - Animal Facility Purchase Orders, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Moffett - I, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Chapel, 1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - E-Quad, 1975-1980; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Forrestal Building 8A, 1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Moffett - Budget and Proposals, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Seegar Arts Center, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - 185 Nassau Street, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Princeton University - Broadmead Housing Study, 1978 August 24; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Princeton Township Master Plan, 1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Natural Resources Inventory of Princeton, 1978; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Regional Planning Board - Plans, 1980; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Buildings - Gross Square Feet, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Classroom Physical Profile Survey #1, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Physical Profile Survey #2, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Lourie-Love Mailroom, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor Green, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Dod Hall, 1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Quad, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Dod Hall - Life Safety/Lounge, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Green Hall, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Stanhope Hall, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Palmer Hall, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Palmer Hall, 1976; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Moffett, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Prospect, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Prospect Hall Alterations, 1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Green Hall Alterations, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Rowing Tank, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Rowing Tank - Municipality, Budget, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Rowing Tank, 1968-1974; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Eno - Geology Library, 1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Green Hall - Ornstein, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - West College, 1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Palmer House - Furniture, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Palmer House Alterations, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Biochemical Sciences Building, 1970-1984; 1 box
    - Budget, 1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Proposals, 1976; 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Site Plans, Photographs, Schematics, Etc, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Hoods, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Testing Laboratories, 1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Survey Borings, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Equipment Brochures, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Distilled Water, 1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Program Minutes, Correspondence, 1976; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - House Moving, 1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Utilities Energy, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Reference Room, Basement Office, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Solvent Store, 1972-1980; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Loading Dock, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Emissions, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Acid Waste Removal, 1973; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Parking, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Agency Approvals, 1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - P-3 Laboratory, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Purchase Orders, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Site Photographs, 1975; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Animal Quarters, 1973; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Architecture Building, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Moffett Laboratory, 1966-1968; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Guyot - Moffett, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Moffett, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Terrace Club Alterations, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Terrace Club - Purchase Orders, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Green Hall - Purchase Orders, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Green Hall - Dr. Kinchla, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Green Hall, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Green Hall - Campbell Lab, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Moffett, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Pyne Hall Alterations, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Jones Hall - Purchase Orders, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Pyne Dorms, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Jones Hall Alterations, 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Inventory Data, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Dormitory Space, 1969; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Mercer County - Generalized Existing Land Use Map, 1969 September; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Mercer County Planning Board - Comprehensive Planning Program, 1968; 1 box
    - Population Factors, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - General Physical Conditions, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Economic Analysis, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Public Facilities and Services, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Storm Water Runoff and Drainage Facilities, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Analysis of Water Supply and Sewerage Facilities, 1968; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Green Hall, 1973; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Green Hall, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Grounds, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Jadwin Gym, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Princeton Inn, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Princeton Inn, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Princeton Inn College, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - McCarter Theater, 1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Green Hall, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Moffett Lab, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - New South, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - 5 Ivy Lane, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Cannon Club, 1973-1978; 1 box
    - Cannon Club, 1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - University #1, 1973; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Consultant #1, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Consultant #2, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Contractor, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - University #2, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Purchase Orders, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Proposal for Joseph Tonetti and Associates, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 1903 Hall, 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Cannon Club, 1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Woodrow Wilson School, 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Woodrow Wilson School, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 185 Nassau Street, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Eno Hall, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Fine Hall, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Jadwin Gym - Office of Public Information, 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Cannon Club - Budget, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Cannon Club - Change Orders and Payments, 1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Engineering Quad Library, 1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Engineering Quad, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 99 Alexander Street, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - McCosh Infirmary, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Palmer Hall, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Macmillan Building, 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 1879 Hall, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Green Hall, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - West College, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Dormitories (Lourie-Love), 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Engineering Quad - Purchase Orders, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Firestone Library, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - McCosh Hall, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Maclean House, 1973; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Palmer Hall - Correspondence, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Palmer Library, 1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Engineering Quad, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Palmer Square Study, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Palmer Hall - Purchase Orders, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - McCosh Infirmary, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Engineering Quad - Correspondence, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Biochemical Sciences Laboratory, 1970-1982; 2 boxes
    - Nassau Court, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Nassau Court, 1978; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Architects' Fees, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Biochemical Sciences Laboratory, 1970-1976; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Sciences Space Report (7566), 1970-1976; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Curriculum Vitae of Faculty, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Consultants, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Humphrey's and Harding, 1976-1982; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous I, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous III, 1979; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1976 April-June; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1976; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Furniture, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous IV, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1976 July-November; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1976 September-1977 February; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Construction, 1978 April-August; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Construction, 1978 November-1979 March; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Construction, 1978 August-October; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1977 February-May; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1977 June-1978 September; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Community, 1977 January-February; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1976 January-1979 October; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Construction, 1978 February-May; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - P-3 Facilities, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Construction, 1977 February-October; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Construction, 1977 November-1978 January; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Proposals, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Budget/Contracts, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Program, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Frick Chemical Lab, 1960-1965; 1 box
    - Addition, 1961-1965; 1 box
      - Addition, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - O'Connor and Kilham, Agreements and Payments, 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - O'Connor and Kilham, Correspondence, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Bidding, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - National Institute of Health, 1962; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Change Orders, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Cold Room, 1963; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Professor Hornig, 1961-1964; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - O'Connor and Kilham Correspondence, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Alterations, 1960-1964; 1 box
      - Alterations, 1961; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - National Institute of Health Grant, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Library - Biology, Geology, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Frick Chemical Lab, 1960-1965; 1 box
    - O'Connor and Kilham, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Alterations, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Matthews Construction Company - Agreements and Payments, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Grants - National Science Foundation, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Progress Schedule, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Addition, 1961-1965; 1 box
      - Concrete Testing, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Furniture, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Keys, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Johnson and Higgins, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Seelye Stevenson/Value and Knecht, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Subcontractors, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Matthews Construction Company - Agreements and Payments, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Plans, Specifications, Budget Estimations, Costs, Etc, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Guggenheim Labs, 1962-1966; 1 box
    - (A-1031), 1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - William C. Ehret - Contract-Payments, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Preliminary Plans and Specifications, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Change Orders, 1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Monthly Reports to NASA, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Insurance, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Progress Photographs, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Solid Propellant Test Stand, 1963; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Scrimenti, Swackhamer and Perantoni, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Guyot Hall, 1957-1966; 1 box
    - #2, Geology Addition - Minutes of Meetings, 1961 June-1965 February; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Furnishings - Geology Wing #2, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Geology Addition, 1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Geology #2 - Seelye, Stevenson/Value and Knecht, Correspondence, 1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Geology Wing - Subcontractors, 1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Biology-Geology Additions/General Correspondence, 1959-1966; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - O'Connor and Kilham - Correspondence, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Matthews Construction Company - Contract, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Matthews Construction Company - Agreements, Payments, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Grants, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Biology Addition, 1958; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - O'Connor and Kilham - Agreements, Payments, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Job Visits, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Plan Transmittals, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Construction, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Geology Addition, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Specifications, 1959-1964; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Alterations, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Geology Addition, 1960-1965; 1 box
      - II (A-1211), 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 46)
      - (A-1211), 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 47)
      - Matthews Construction Company - Contract-Payments, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 48)